Using Pygame
Transform an image into block characters with BBCODE for forums giving the right colors to the right blocks
(foreground color only)

Like this:
[color=#2b41eb]█[/color]

/!\SMALL/!\ 
It is often too long for forums however... use on small images!
/!\PIXELS/!\ 
Cannot represent two colored pixels on top of eachother (for every 2 lines) except if one is transparent.
/!\TRANSPARENT/!\ 
Works better if background color is transparent (because the "2 adjacent colors" thing works if there is no color).


If you want to change the color of the "transparent" lines, you can wrap all the result into a [color=white] [/color] thing.

If you can also manage your background color, you would be able to represent any image (not done here...)
but if you have that freedom, why not just put an image?


Bug:
	libpng warning: bKGD: invalid index

When I add transparency in GraphicsGale
Usually fixed by using pngoptimiser on the .png